<Document>
[head=3][color=#ff0000]WARNING: You must be 18 or older to play. Users under 18 will be banned immediately.[/head][/color]

[color=#99ff99]T.E. Sector is an english speaking 18+ medium-high roleplay server[/color]

[color=#a4885c][head=3]0. Implimentation and interpretation of the rules is up to the sole discretion of the Admins.[/head][/color]
	
	• Admins will instead be held accountable through use of the Admin code of conduct. 

[color=#ffff00]If you have any questions about these rules, please use the Admin help menu by hitting F1 in-game, or clicking the "AHelp" button in the lobby, or alternatively, ask for assistance on the discord.[/color]


  Each section contains its own list of rules. Click on the section name to view the full version.

  - [textlink="Section 1. General rules" link="RuleC1"]
  - [textlink="Section 2. GOLDEN rules" link="RuleC2"]
    
[color=#ffff00][head=3]Section 1: General Rules[/head][/color]

[color=#a4885c]1.1[/color] Be respectful to others OOC. 

[color=#a4885c]1.2[/color] While more conflict is allowed, a 5-minute notice should be given when intending to raid, fine, or otherwise board a vessel. Including declaration of intents, such as looting, fining, searching or kidnapping.

[color=#a4885c]1.3[/color] No murderboning or killing without reason [duh] 

[color=#a4885c]1.4[/color] Factions should be traveling together, rather than seperated to ensure protection and adequate cover. While not directly a rule, prevents silly issues like going alone and simply dying.

[color=#a4885c]1.5[/color] The central sector, or where the outpost for docking ships/buying supplies/loading a ship is done, has a 500m x 500m safezone around it. Meaning any conflict should be avoided in this region. But a vessel fleeing into the safezone after being hailed/informed of a boarding, is fair game.

[color=#a4885c]1.6[/color] Factions can only engage in all-out war when all faction ships agree to it, and when doing so, independants should not take any part. 

[color=#a4885c]1.7[/color] IF you are not part of a fight, or are not of the same faction of whoever's being attacked, YOU CANNOT TAKE PART. If you are SHOT AT, you simply still cannot fight. You cannot use getting into the crossfire as a reason for fighting either. 

[color=#a4885c]1.8[/color] KIDNAPPING: Since this is an ERP server, if players consent via LOOC/OOC notes in their profile, they can be kidnapped, and kept by the raiding party for sexual things until otherwise is said, or an Ahelp is made. 

[color=#a4885c]1.9[/color] Have an interesting gimmick and are less interested in grinding 3 hours to get to it? Ahelp! Provided you're not inherently powergaming, or just looking for an advantage over others, getting a helping hand to skip some of the grind in favor for roleplaying with others is more than fine!

[color=#FFD700][head=3]Section 2: GOLDEN Rules[/head][/color] 

[color=#FFD700]1.1[/color] We're all adults here, and if you have a certain idea you want to do with other players, the best place to arrange it, is at the outpost! The outpost is like an OOC zone, so you can freely approach and use LOOC to come up with ideas if not done in OOC already. Players aren't forced to fight, and they aren't forced to be victims either. We're all here to have fun, and you can choose not to take part in certain aspects despite what's allowed above.

[color=#FFD700]1.2[/color] Communicate if something isn't what you want it to be! Using arepee-planning on the discord is also one way to go about it, so don't be shy to try out ideas with other people. 

[color=#FFD700]1.3[/color] For example, if you want to have a skirmish without removing each other, or one of the ships entirely, could even ask an admin to make sure the involved parties are healed after the conflict, allowing story progression without crippling consequences, provided it is what they'd like! How you play it out is your way, could consider it ICly being re-cloned, or being shipped in as a new member!
</Document>
